

AJRAT SHARMA

PROFILE

Well organized, creative, and confident. Open to working with and across sales teams and well as external clients and agencies on creative, editorial, strategic, and tactical levels. Significant negotiation experience with a will of delivering unique and effective content. Impressive history of planning and executing campaigns

CONTACT

PHONE: 8284062881

LINKEDIN:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/ajratkumar-sharma-442820258/

EMAIL:

ajratsh123@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Communication skills
- Multi-task Management
- Inter-personal skills
- Management Skills
- Strong Creative Vision
- Computer Literate
- Pressure handling

WORK EXPERIENCE

MARKETING AND SALES EXECUTIVE GOODWILL PHARMACY, LUDHIANA

JULY 2019-JULY 2020

Work with clients to craft the messaging and implement strategic positioning in their market. Assist clients with business plan, sales, and marketing. Devised and implemented social media. Create marketing campaigns including email, digital and social media.

HR ASSISTANT JNS INSTRUMENTS LTD, GURGAON

JUNE 2022-JULY 2022

Led talent acquisition for the company, worked on creating new leads and conducted employ onboarding. Filtered resumes and finalized candidates suitable for the job profiles for the company. Coordinated and scheduled interviews to the prospective candidates. managed work calendar and worked with the team for further developments.

EDUCATION

BACHLEOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION LOVELY PROFESSIONAL UNIVERSITY, PUNJAB 2020-2023

cgpa - 8.24 /10

HIGHER SECONDARY EDUCATION IPS LUDHIANA (ISCE) -2019
Percentage secured - 78.00%

HIGH SCHOOL SKPS LUDHIANA (CBSE) -2019 Percentage Secured – 84.00%